Guide to the John Farquhar Fulton Papers
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- General Files, 1910-1960; Series I
  - Sprague, James M., 1943-1954 (Box 162, Folder 2323)
  - Spurling, R. Glen, 1933-1960 (Box 162, Folder 2324-2325)
  - Spurr, Gerald Baxter, 1950 (Box 162, Folder 2326)
  - Stansill, Helen N., 1952-1953 (Box 162, Folder 2327)
  - Stanton, Madeline E.
    - 1928-1939 (Box 162, Folder 2328-2333)
    - 1941-1960 (Box 163, Folder 2334-2342)
  - Starbuck, Helen, 1938-1945 (Box 163, Folder 2343)
  - Starr, Albert M., 1950 (Box 163, Folder 2344)
  - Stecher, Robert M., 1936-1959 (Box 163, Folder 2345)
  - Steenhoff, Barbara, 1948 (Box 163, Folder 2346)
  - Stefansson, Vilhjlamur
    See also: box 81, folders 1131-1136
    See also: box 82, folder 1143-1145
    - 1957 July-October (Box 163, Folder 2347)
    - 1957 November-1959 (Box 164, Folder 2348)
  - Steiman, Iser, 1942-1960 (Box 164, Folder 2349-2350)
  - Steiner, Walter R., 1930-1940 (Box 164, Folder 2351)
  - Stephenson, Charles S., 1940-1951 (Box 164, Folder 2352-2356)
    See also: Series II, box 236, folders 626
    See also: series II, boxes 237-240, folders 640-687
    See also: series II, boxes 241-246, folders 706-766
  - Stern, Eve W., 1949-1955 (Box 165, Folder 2357)
  - Stern, Kurt G., 1936-1952 (Box 165, Folder 2358)
  - Stevens, Herman C., 1928-1934 (Box 165, Folder 2359)
  - Stevenson, James A. F., 1948-1958 (Box 165, Folder 2360)
  - Stevenson, Lloyd G., 1952-1960 (Box 165, Folder 2361-2362)
  - Stever, Robert T., 1945-1960 (Box 165, Folder 2363)
  - Stewart, George, 1933-1960 (Box 165, Folder 2364)
    See also: boxes 48-52, folders 706-766
  - Stimson, Dorothy, 1932-1959 (Box 165, Folder 2365)
  - Stone, Edward L., 1930 (Box 165, Folder 2366)
  - Stone, William, 1950 (Box 165, Folder 2367)
  - Straus, William L., Jr., 1931-1942 (Box 165, Folder 2368)
  - Strong, Leonell C., n.d. (Box 165, Folder 2369)
  - Stubbs, S. G. Blaxland, 1931 (Box 165, Folder 2370)
  - Stubbs Society, 1923-1924 (Box 165, Folder 2371)
  - Sullivan, Helen, 1935-1938 (Box 165, Folder 2372)
  - Sundstrom, Edward S., 1942 (Box 166, Folder 2373)
  - Surgery, Gynecology, and Obstetrics, 1928-1934 (Box 166, Folder 2374)
  - Swanson, Homer, 1940 (Box 166, Folder 2375)
  - Swanson, Virginia L., 1947-1948 (Box 166, Folder 2376)
  - Sweet, William H., 1935-1953 (Box 166, Folder 2377)
  - Szent-Gyorgyi, Albert, 1929-1949 (Box 166, Folder 2378)
  - Szentagothai, John, 1948-1959 (Box 166, Folder 2379)
  - Ta (Box 166, Folder 2380)
  - Te-Th (Box 166, Folder 2381)
  - Ti-To (Box 166, Folder 2382)
  - Tr-Tz (Box 166, Folder 2383)
  - Tait, Columbus Downing, Jr., 1947-1958 (Box 166, Folder 2384)
  - Tallmadge, G. Kasten, 1952-1960 (Box 166, Folder 2385)
  - Tarlov, I. M., 1936 (Box 166, Folder 2386)
  - Tator, Barbara, 1942-1943 (Box 166, Folder 2387)
  - Taussig, Helen, 1940-1941 (Box 166, Folder 2388)
  - Taylor, Dermot B., 1948-1955 (Box 166, Folder 2389)
  - Taylor, T. W. J., 1943-1944 (Box 166, Folder 2390)
  - Technical, Scientific and Medical Bibliography
    See: series II, boxes 231-232, folders 534-538
  - Temkin, Owsei
    See also: series II, box 240-246, folders 706-766
    - 1933-1944 (Box 166, Folder 2391)
    - 1946-1959 (Box 167, Folder 2392)
  - Tepperman, Jay, 1945-1952 (Box 167, Folder 2393)
  - Thaler, Alwin, 1931 (Box 167, Folder 2394)
  - Thayer, William S., 1928-1932 (Box 167, Folder 2395)
  - Thewlis, Malford, 1932-1933 (Box 167, Folder 2396)
  - This Month in American Medicine, 1946-1947 (Box 167, Folder 2397)
  - Thomas, Charles C.
    See: boxes 31-35, folders 440-506
  - Thomas Nelson and Sons, Ltd., 1959-1960 (Box 167, Folder 2398)
  - Thompson, Daniel V., 1931-1954 (Box 167, Folder 2399)
  - Thompson, I. Maclaran (Box 167, Folder 2400)
  - Thoms, Herbert, 1931-1960 (Box 167, Folder 2401)
  - Thomson, Elizabeth H.
    - 1944-1957 (Box 167, Folder 2402-2405)
    - 1958-1959 (Box 168, Folder 2406)
  - Thompson, Kenneth W., 1935-1959 (Box 168, Folder 2407)
  - Thompson, Raymond K., 1946-1951 (Box 168, Folder 2408)
  - Thorn, George W., 1939-1958 (Box 168, Folder 2409)
  - Thorndike, Lynn, 1944-1960 (Box 168, Folder 2410)
  - Thorner, Melvin W., 1940-1946 (Box 168, Folder 2411)
    See also: box 5, folders 69-74
    See also: box 156, folder 2222
  - Tillisch, Jan H., 1942-1943 (Box 168, Folder 2412)
  - Tilney, Frederick, 1924-1937 (Box 168, Folder 2413)
  - Tinker, Chauncey B., 1931-1953 (Box 168, Folder 2414)
  - Titanium Alloy Manufacturing Co., 1946-1948 (Box 168, Folder 2415)
  - Tobey, Sally, 1953 (Box 168, Folder 2416)
  - Todd, T. Wingate, 1925-1935 (Box 168, Folder 2417)
  - Tokizane, Toshihiko, 1955-1956 (Box 168, Folder 2418)
  - Tournay, Auguste, 1929-1959 (Box 168, Folder 2419)
  - Tower, Sarah F., 1929-1952 (Box 168, Folder 2420-2421)
  - Transatlantic Foundation Group, 1946 (Box 169, Folder 2422)
  - Trent, Josiah C., 1941-1955 (Box 169, Folder 2423-2424)
  - Truesdale Hospital, 1949 (Box 169, Folder 2425)
  - Trueta, Josep, 1940-1959 (Box 169, Folder 2426)
  - Tudor and Stuart Club, 1926-1932 (Box 169, Folder 2427)
  - Turkel, Henry, 1960 (Box 169, Folder 2428)
  - Turnbull, Andrew W., 1958-1959 (Box 169, Folder 2429)
  - Turner, Eric A., 1951-1957 (Box 169, Folder 2430)
  - Turner, Kenneth, 1944-1945 (Box 169, Folder 2431)
  - Turner, Oscar, 1934-1947 (Box 169, Folder 2432)
  - Twitchell, Thomas Evans, 1947-1960 (Box 169, Folder 2433)
  - U (Box 169, Folder 2434)
  - Underwood, Edgar Ashworth, 1946-1955 (Box 169, Folder 2435)
    See also: box 179, folder 2671
  - Underwood, Eric, 1939-1949 (Box 169, Folder 2436)
  - United Kingdom Home Office, Whitehall, 1922-1930 (Box 170, Folder 2437)
  - United States. Customs Service, 1931-1941 (Box 170, Folder 2438)
  - United States. Department of Justice, 1959 (Box 170, Folder 2439)
  - United States. Department of State: passports, 1931-1940 (Box 170, Folder 2440)
  - United States. Executive Office of the President. Committee on Records of War Administration, 1944 (Box 170, Folder 2441)
  - United States. Executive Office of the President. Office of Scientific Research and Development, 1940-1946 (Box 170, Folder 2442)
  - United States. Federal Security Agency, 1941-1946 (Box 170, Folder 2443)
  - United States. Government Printing Office, 1927-1936 (Box 170, Folder 2444)
  - United States. Navy. "Operation Everest,", 1946-1947 (Box 170, Folder 2445)
  - United States. Public Health Service, 1939-1946 (Box 170, Folder 2446)
  - United States. Surgeon General's Office, 1935-1942 (Box 170, Folder 2447)
  - United States. War Manpower Commission, 1942-1944 (Box 170, Folder 2448)
  - University of Louisville: Innominate Society, 1940-1941 (Box 170, Folder 2449)
  - University of Minnesota Medical School, 1932-1936 (Box 170, Folder 2550)
  - University of Oregon, 1941-1942 (Box 170, Folder 2551)
  - University of Pennsylvania Press, 1950-1953 (Box 170, Folder 2552)
  - University of Toronto, 1940-1941 (Box 170, Folder 2553)
  - Ünver, A. Süneyl, 1954-1959 (Box 170, Folder 2554)
  - Uotila, Unto U., 1939-1940 (Box 170, Folder 2555)
  - Urba, Hubert, 1939-1950 (Box 170, Folder 2556)
  - Urdang, George, 1944-1957 (Box 170, Folder 2557)
  - V (Box 171, Folder 2558)
  - Valentine, Alan, 1935-1956 (Box 171, Folder 2559)
  - Vanderbilt University: Phi Beta Pi, 1940-1941 (Box 171, Folder 2560)
  - Van Gehuchten, Paul, 1949-1955 (Box 171, Folder 2561)
  - Van Itallie, Theodore, 1953-1955 (Box 171, Folder 2562)
  - Van Sinderen, Adrian, 1956-1959 (Box 171, Folder 2563)
  - Van Wagenen, Gertrude, 1928-1960 (Box 171, Folder 2564-2566)
  - Van Wagenen, William P., 1933-1954 (Box 171, Folder 2567)
  - Vargas, Valentin, 1959-1960 (Box 171, Folder 2568)
  - Vasconselos, Ivolino de, 1951-1958 (Box 171, Folder 2569)
  - Vasiliu, D. O., 1934-1948 (Box 171, Folder 2570)
  - Vaudrin, Philip, 1946-1954 (Box 171, Folder 2571)
  - Veeder, Borden, 1957-1959 (Box 171, Folder 2572)
  - Veith, Ilza, 1953-1960 (Box 171, Folder 2573)
  - Velardo, Joseph, 1958-1960 (Box 171, Folder 2574)
  - Velden, Oswald, 1943 (Box 171, Folder 2575)
  - Verdourn, Frans, 1948-1956 (Box 171, Folder 2576)
  - Verhaart, Willem Josef Cornelius, 1935-1959 (Box 172, Folder 2577)
  - Victorius, Paul, 1931-1935 (Box 172, Folder 2578)
  - Viebranz, Marion, 1930-1931 (Box 172, Folder 2579)
  - Viets, Henry
    See also: box 22, folders 305-306
    - 1925-1934 (Box 172, Folder 2580-2585)
    - 1935-1943 (Box 173, Folder 2586-2593)
    - 1944-1960 (Box 174, Folder 2594-2598)
  - Vincent, Clovis, 1929-1934 (Box 174, Folder 2599)
  - Vishnu, 1948-1952 (Box 174, Folder 2600)
  - Visscher, Maurice C., 1931-1932, 1954, 1959 (Box 174, Folder 2601)
  - Vogt, Oskar and Cécile, 1935-1939, 1947 (Box 174, Folder 2602)
  - Von Bonin, Gerhardt, 1938-1952 (Box 174, Folder 2603)
  - Vonderahe, A. R., 1939-1941 (Box 174, Folder 2604)
  - Wac-Wal (Box 174, Folder 2605)
  - War-Waw (Box 175, Folder 2606)
  - Wea-Wei (Box 175, Folder 2607)
  - Wel-Wey (Box 175, Folder 2608)
  - Wh (Box 175, Folder 2609)
  - Wid-Wil (Box 175, Folder 2610)
  - Wim-Wit (Box 175, Folder 2611)
  - Wo (Box 175, Folder 2612)
  - Wr-Wy (Box 175, Folder 2613)
  - W. B. Saunders Co., 1930-1960 (Box 175, Folder 2614-2615)
    See also: boxes 221-226, folders 373-466
  - W. W. Norton and Co., 1928-1957 (Box 176, Folder 2616-2617)
  - Wagman, Irving, 1953-1959 (Box 176, Folder 2618)
  - Wakerlin, George, 1941-1952 (Box 176, Folder 2619)
  - Walker, Arthur Earl, 1934-1959 (Box 176, Folder 2620-2623)
  - Walker, Arthur M., 1941-1942 (Box 176, Folder 2624)
  - Walker, W. Cameron, 1934-1937 (Box 176, Folder 2625)
  - Walker, William B., 1948-1954 (Box 176, Folder 2626)
  - Wall, Florence, 1937, 1948, 1957 (Box 176, Folder 2627)
  - Wall, Patrick D., 1948-1960 (Box 176, Folder 2628)
  - Walls, Milton, 1929-1953 (Box 177, Folder 2629)
  - Wallum, Charlotte, 1930-1957 (Box 177, Folder 2630)
  - Walshe, Francis, 1925-1959 (Box 177, Folder 2631)
  - Wang, Ging Hsi, 1944-1960 (Box 177, Folder 2632)
  - Wang, Shih-Chun, 1939-1955 (Box 177, Folder 2633)
  - Wangensteen, Owen, 1931-1960 (Box 177, Folder 2634)
  - Ward, Arthur A., 1943-1959 (Box 177, Folder 2635)
  - Ward, Roswell, 1948-1953 (Box 177, Folder 2636)
  - Waring, James, 1932-1958 (Box 177, Folder 2637)
  - Warren, Stafford, 1948-1951, 1958 (Box 177, Folder 2638)
  - Wartenberg, Robert, 1942-1955 (Box 177, Folder 2639)
  - Waters, Levin, 1954-1960 (Box 177, Folder 2640)
  - Watley, Vernon, 1949-1959 (Box 177, Folder 2641)
  - Watts, James W.
    - 1931-1934 (Box 177, Folder 2642)
    - 1935-1955 (Box 178, Folder 2643-2644)
  - Webster, Jerome, 1934-1951 (Box 178, Folder 2645)
  - Wechsler, Israel, 1932-1957 (Box 178, Folder 2646)
  - Weddell, Graham, 1943-1948 (Box 178, Folder 2647)
  - Weed, Lewis
    See also: box 232, folders 543-544
    - 1927-1944 (Box 178, Folder 2648-2655)
    - 1945-1952 (Box 179, Folder 2656-2659)
  - Weeks, Carnes, 1959-1960 (Box 179, Folder 2660)
  - Weeks, Edward, 1958 (Box 179, Folder 2661)
  - Weikert, Margaret, 1927-1932 (Box 179, Folder 2662)
  - Weil, Ernest, 1940-1960 (Box 179, Folder 2663)
  - Weinstein, B. Bernard, 1939-1956 (Box 179, Folder 2664)
  - Weinstein, Edwin A., 1938-1959 (Box 179, Folder 2665)
  - Weiss, Paul, 1942-1948 (Box 179, Folder 2666)
  - Weiss, Soma, 1929-1936 (Box 179, Folder 2667)
  - Welch, William, 1932 (Box 179, Folder 2668)
  - Welch Bibliophilic Society, 1934-1939 (Box 179, Folder 2669)
  - Weldon, Harry, 1928-1954 (Box 179, Folder 2670)
  - Wellcome Historical Medical Museum, 1947-1950 (Box 179, Folder 2671)
  - Wendt, G. Richard, 1934-1958 (Box 179, Folder 2672)
  - Werner, Attie Yvonne, 1948-1956 (Box 180, Folder 2673)
  - West Hamilton Street Club, 1940-1949 (Box 180, Folder 2674)
  - Western, Fred, 1939-1941 (Box 180, Folder 2675)
  - Wheatland, Ann, 1921-1923 (Box 180, Folder 2676)
  - Wheatland, David P. and family [includes Barbara and Susan], 1924-1960 (Box 180, Folder 2677)
  - Wheatland, Martha [sister of Lucia Fulton], 1923-1929 (Box 180, Folder 2678)
  - Wheatland, Mary and Richard [parents of Lucia Fulton]
    - 1916, 1921-1932 (Box 180, Folder 2679-2683)
    - 1933-1960 (Box 181, Folder 2684-2690)
  - Wheatland, Stephen and family [includes Richard Jr., Sarah, and Mary]
    - 1921-1950 (Box 181, Folder 2691)
    - 1951-1960 (Box 182, Folder 2692)
  - Wheaton, Annabelle, 1923 (Box 182, Folder 2693)
  - Wheaton, Olive, 1931-1932 (Box 182, Folder 2694)
  - Wheaton-Smith, Franklin, 1924-1946 (Box 182, Folder 2695)
  - Wheaton-Smith family, 1938-1947 (Box 182, Folder 2696)
  - Wheeler, Mary, 1937-1960, undated (Box 182, Folder 2697-2699)
  - Whieldon, John, 1948-1956 (Box 182, Folder 2700)
  - Whipple, George, 1926-1940 (Box 182, Folder 2701)
  - White, Abraham, 1947-1953 (Box 182, Folder 2702)
  - White, James, 1929-1956 (Box 182, Folder 2703)
  - White, Paul Dudley, 1926-1956 (Box 182, Folder 2704)
  - White, Sarah, 1944-1949, 1958-1959 (Box 182, Folder 2705)
  - Whitmore, Alice (Cheney), 1931-1932 (Box 182, Folder 2706)
  - Whitney, Leon, 1936-1938, 1950 (Box 182, Folder 2707)
  - Whitteridge, D., 1952-1957 (Box 182, Folder 2708)
  - Whittingham, Harold, 1940-1957 (Box 183, Folder 2709-2711)
  - Whittock, Ruth, 1932-1934 (Box 183, Folder 2712)
  - Whitty, C. W. M., 1948-1957 (Box 183, Folder 2713)
  - Wiegendruck Gesellschaft, 1930-1937 (Box 183, Folder 2714)
  - Wigderson, Henry, 1935-1952 (Box 183, Folder 2715)
  - Wiggers, Carl, 1927-1955 (Box 183, Folder 2716)
  - Wiggers, Harold, 1936-1943 (Box 183, Folder 2717)
  - Wigmore, Ethel, 1940-1949 (Box 183, Folder 2718)
  - Wikler, Abraham, 1942-1960 (Box 183, Folder 2719)
  - Wilder, Isabel, 1937-1957 (Box 183, Folder 2720)
  - Wilder, Thornton, 1937-1951 (Box 183, Folder 2721)
  - Wildes, Marjorie, 1929-1935 (Box 183, Folder 2722)
  - Wilkinson, Herbert, 1929-1931 (Box 183, Folder 2723)
  - William H. Welch Medical Library
  - Williams, Clyde, 1951-1954 (Box 183, Folder 2724)
  - Williams, John, 1941-1950 (Box 183, Folder 2725)
  - Williams, Vernon, 1931-1946 (Box 183, Folder 2726)
  - Williams and Wilkins Co., 1925-1950 (Box 184, Folder 2727-2728)
  - William Welch Society, N. Y. U. College of Medicine, 1943 (Box 184, Folder 2729)
  - Wilson, Carroll, 1937-1945 (Box 184, Folder 2730)
  - Wilson, Charles, 1939-1940 (Box 184, Folder 2731)
  - Wilson, J. Walter, 1940-1944 (Box 184, Folder 2732)
  - Wilson, May, 1936-1937 (Box 184, Folder 2733)
  - Windle, William, 1942-1960 (Box 184, Folder 2734)
  - Wing, Donald, 1936-1959 (Box 184, Folder 2735)
  - Winser, David, 1938-1939 (Box 184, Folder 2736)
  - Winslow, Charles-Edward, 1931-1951 (Box 184, Folder 2737)
  - Winternitz, Milton C., 1937-1958 (Box 184, Folder 2738)
  - Winzler, Richard J., 1938-1958 (Box 184, Folder 2739)
  - Wise, Bowman, 1938 (Box 184, Folder 2740)
  - Wise, Robert, 1941-1956 (Box 184, Folder 2741)
  - Wislocki, George, 1931-1959 (Box 184, Folder 2742)
  - Wistar Institute, 1933-1941 (Box 184, Folder 2743)
  - Witten, Lawrence, 1952-1959 (Box 184, Folder 2744)
  - Wolfe, Harold, 1931-1933 (Box 184, Folder 2745)
  - Wood, Casey, 1937-1940 (Box 185, Folder 2746)
  - Wood, Ellen, 1920-1941 (Box 185, Folder 2747)
  - Wood, Harry T., Jr., 1950 (Box 185, Folder 2748)
  - Woodhall, Frances, 1930-1933 (Box 185, Folder 2749)
  - Woodhall, M. Barnes, 1931-1960 (Box 185, Folder 2750)
  - Woolsey, Clinton, 1934-1957 (Box 185, Folder 2751)
  - Worthington, Ruth, 1952-1955 (Box 185, Folder 2752)
  - Wortis, Sam Bernard, 1936-1949 (Box 185, Folder 2753)
  - Wright, George Payling, 1924-1928 (Box 185, Folder 2754)
  - Wright, Joyce, 1924-1937 (Box 185, Folder 2755)
  - Wright, Samson, 1930-1953 (Box 185, Folder 2756)
  - Wright, Wilmer C., 1935-1940 (Box 185, Folder 2757)
  - Wrinch, Dorothy, 1936-1951 (Box 185, Folder 2758)
  - Wroth, Lawrence, 1937-1957 (Box 185, Folder 2759)
  - Wylie, Francis and Kathleen, 1934-1956 (Box 185, Folder 2760)
  - Wynne-Finch, Heneage, 1934-1935 (Box 185, Folder 2761)
  - Wyss, Oscar A. M., 1935-1959 (Box 185, Folder 2762-2764)
  - Y (Box 185, Folder 2765)
  - Yaglou, C. P., 1942-1944 (Box 186, Folder 2766)
  - Yakovlev, Paul, 1933-1959 (Box 186, Folder 2767)
  - Yale Daily News, 1952-1953 (Box 186, Folder 2768)
  - Yale Interprets the News, 1943, 1944, 1945 (Box 186, Folder 2769)
  - Yale Journal of Biology and Medicine, 1930-1947 (Box 186, Folder 2770)
  - Yale Library Associates, 1933-1960 (Box 186, Folder 2771)
  - Yale Library Gazette, 1930-1939 (Box 186, Folder 2772)
  - Yale Review, 1931-1934, 1947-1948 (Box 186, Folder 2773)
  - Yale University
    - General, 1931-1950 (Box 186, Folder 2774)
    - Art Gallery, 1946 (Box 186, Folder 2775)
    - Committee on Honorary Degrees (Box 186, Folder 2776)
    - Committee on University Policy as to Federal Support of Scientific Research, 1945 (Box 186, Folder 2777)
    - Coxe Scholarship Committee, 1932-1938 (Box 186, Folder 2778)
    - Graduate School, 1930-1936 (Box 186, Folder 2779)
    - Henry Fellowships, 1931-1938 (Box 186, Folder 2880)
    - John Addison Porter Prize, 1935 (Box 186, Folder 2881)
    - Library, 1930-1960 (Box 187, Folder 2882-2884)
    - News Bureau, 1948-1960 (Box 187, Folder 2885)
    - Pierson College, 1935-1959 (Box 187, Folder 2886)
    - President (Box 187, Folder 2887)
      See also: box 8, Folder 114
    - School of Medicine
      - General, 1932-1960 (Box 187, Folder 2888)
      - Adolescence Study Unit, 1935-1941 (Box 187, Folder 2889)
      - Committees
        - Appointments, 1931-1932, 1948-1949 (Box 187, Folder 2890)
        - Biological Sciences, 1930-1951 (Box 187, Folder 2891)
        - Curriculum, 1939-1941 (Box 187, Folder 2892)
        - Deanships, 1940 (Box 187, Folder 2893)
        - Department of Anatomy, 1931-1933 (Box 187, Folder 2894)
        - Library, 1930-1938 (Box 188, Folder 2895)
        - Pharmacology, 1932-1937 (Box 188, Folder 2896)
        - Physical Medicine, 1946-1949 (Box 188, Folder 2897)
        - Physiological Chemistry, 1935-1936 (Box 188, Folder 2898)
        - Psychiatry (Box 188, Folder 2899)
        - Rehabilitation Medicine, 1947-1949 (Box 188, Folder 2900)
        - School of Medicine, 1932-1935 (Box 188, Folder 2901)
      - Deans
        See also: box 191, folder 2935
        - 1928-1950 (Box 188, Folder 2902-2906)
        - 1951-1960 (Box 189, Folder 2907-2908)
      - Department of Physiology
        - Annual Report
          - 1930-1946 (Box 189, Folder 2909-2918)
          - 1946-1950 (Box 190, Folder 2919-2922)
        - Budget, 1926-1934, 1940 (Box 190, Folder 2923)
        - History, 1930-1950 (Box 190, Folder 2924)
      - Executive Secretary, Bishop, Lottie G., 1929-1953, undated (Box 190, Folder 2925-2928)
      - History of Medicine, 1945-1961 (Box 191, Folder 2929)
      - Medical Library, Digby Collection., 1943-1960 (Box 191, Folder 2930)
      - Medical Society, 1930-1959 (Box 191, Folder 2931-2932)
      - Neurological Study Unit, 1930-1960 (Box 191, Folder 2933)
      - Postgraduate Courses for Physicians, 1932-1959 (Box 191, Folder 2934)
      - Prudential Committee, 1937 (Box 191, Folder 2935)
      - Registrar, 1929-1935 (Box 191, Folder 2936)
    - Secretary, 1930-1960 (Box 191, Folder 2937)
    - Seessel Fellowship Committee, 1932-1952 (Box 191, Folder 2938)
    - Sheffield Scientific School, 1931-1932 (Box 191, Folder 2939)
    - Silliman Lecture, 1950-1958 (Box 191, Folder 2940)
    - Sterling Fellowship Committee, 1933-1940 (Box 191, Folder 2941)
    - Terry Lecture, 1931-1950 (Box 191, Folder 2942)
    - Treasurer, 1929-1944 (Box 191, Folder 2943)
    - Undergraduate Lecture Committee, 1959 (Box 191, Folder 2944)
    - University Council's Committee on the Press, 1931-1934 (Box 191, Folder 2945)
    - University Fellowships, 1933-1937 (Box 191, Folder 2946)
  - Yale University Press, 1930-1958 (Box 191, Folder 2947)
  - Year Book Publishers Inc., 1945-1946 (Box 192, Folder 2948)
    See also: box 209, folder 245
  - Yerkes, Robert, 1929-1956 (Box 192, Folder 2949-2951)
  - Yoo, Athanasius, 1956 (Box 192, Folder 2952)
  - Young, Anna C. W., 1947-1955 (Box 192, Folder 2953)
  - Young, Ina Maureen, 1949-1960 (Box 192, Folder 2954)
  - Young, John, 1931-1958 (Box 192, Folder 2955)
  - Yugend, Dorothy, 1931-1932 (Box 192, Folder 2956)
  - Z (Box 192, Folder 2957)
  - Zacharias, Leona, 1943 (Box 192, Folder 2958)
  - Zádor, Imre, 1957 (Box 192, Folder 2959)
  - Zangwill, Oliver L., 1953-1958 (Box 192, Folder 2960)
  - Zehnder, Max, 1945-1952 (Box 192, Folder 2961)
  - Zeitlin, Jacob, 1953-1960 (Box 192, Folder 2962)
  - Zieper, Irving, 1949-1956 (Box 193, Folder 2963)
  - Zimmerman, Harry M., 1931-1940 (Box 193, Folder 2694)
  - Zondek, Bernhard, 1943-1960 (Box 193, Folder 2965)
  - Zotterman, Lena, 1950-1952 (Box 193, Folder 2966)
  - Zotterman, Yngve, 1940-1959 (Box 193, Folder 2967-2968)
  - Zschiesche, Elizabeth, 1938 (Box 193, Folder 2969)
  - Zuckerman, Solly
    See also: box 203, folder 93
    - 1931-1943 (Box 193, Folder 2970-2973)
    - 1944-1960 (Box 194, Folder 2974-2976)
  - Zulch, Klaus-Joachim, 1948-1950 (Box 194, Folder 2977)
  - Zwanenburg, S., 1915, 1931 (Box 194, Folder 2978)
  - Unidentified (Box 194, Folder 2979)
  - Christmas letters, 1938-1959 (Box 194, Folder 2980-2985)
  - Mill Rock Clarion, 1937 (Box 194, Folder 2986)
- Special Subjects, 1892-1965; Series II
  This series contains files for fourteen major organizations and projects in which Fulton was an active participant. These files reflect themes in Fulton's career: bibliophilia relating to science and medicine, service to country, research interests in physiology, and contributions to scholarship through editorial work. The files are arranged in alphabetical order.
  Fulton's life-long interest in books is demonstrated in several projects. Files under the heading "Bibliophilia" include correspondence, catalog listings, price quotations, invoices, and receipts from more than 150 book dealers starting in the 1920s. These files comprise one-fourth of the series. Further evidence of Fulton's interest in medical bibliography can be found in the files "Army Medical Library." These date from Fulton's presidency of the Army Medical Library's Association of Honorary Consultants and his chairmanship of its executive committee, when Fulton campaigned for the building of a national medical library and the preparation of a catalog of medical incunabula. Other bibliographic pursuits resulted in publications. Fulton had a strong collection of the work of the English physicist Robert Boyle. The "Boyle, Robert" files include booksellers' correspondence, as well as drafts and working files for several published bibliographies. Fulton's work on a census of the publication of the theologian and physician Michael Servetus and the completion of Harvey Cushing's bio-bibliography of anatomist Andreas Vesalius are also documented (see "Servetus, Michael" and "Vesalius, Andreas").
  Fulton and Cushing shared interests in bibliography and medicine and worked together, first at Harvard and then at Yale. The files under the heading "Cushing, Harvey" show Fulton's devotion to his mentor. These include the organizational materials for Cushing's seventieth birthday celebration, birthday volume, and bibliography. There are also files from Fulton's involvement in the arrangements for Cushing's funeral, the handling of his estate, and memorial tributes. Files from the early 1940s relate to Fulton's oversight of Cushing's travel memoir, LePuy Diary. The files associated with Fulton's full-length study Harvey Cushing, a Biography constitute the largest portion under this heading. They include copies of advertising notices to help collect information and the responses received. There is also a separate alphabetical sequence of correspondence with publishers vying for the opportunity to publish the biography. Laudatory post-publication correspondence is included in two bound volumes.